[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
(All characters and organisations in this drama are fictional.)
(Filming with minors followed broadcast guidelines,)
(and generative AI was used in select scenes.)
I think this is our first formal introduction.
Yes.
Hello, Han Gyu Oh.
I am Kim Mu Jin, your new older brother as of today.
South Korea is a democratic country,
and in a democracy,
you have the freedom to choose your profession, but...
Working at a host bar is a bit much, is it not?
(Episode 19)
Wipe it.
Wipe the blood.
Did Han Gyu Seo tell you?
Is that important?
It is about hiding it from Gyu Rim,
is it not?
Gyu Rim does not know. And she will not know in the future.
I will make sure she never finds out no matter what.
If she ever finds out...
I will beat you so badly...
you will be completely unrecognizable.
These are written confessions. One is from Son Ji Yeol,
and the other is from your host bar manager.
For your information,
Son Ji Yeol is almost completely back to normal.
He is perfectly fine now, even healthy enough...
to travel to Hawaii.
Talk about needing another surgery was a complete lie.
He, his wife, and your host bar manager conspired...
to scam you and extort your money under various excuses.
I am tired of explaining it,
so read it and see for yourself.
(Written Confession: I, Son Ji Yeol...)
They were even surprised among themselves...
by your stupidity and ignorance.
You are 28 years old.
How could you not suspect a thing...
having your hard-earned money extorted for eight years?
How could you not verify it even once?
They said they'd never seen...
such a gullible fool like you before.
Is there something wrong with your brain?
Do you want to take a cognitive ability test or something?
Hey.
You will not be able to find them even if you go right now.
They turned themselves in to the police...
because they were afraid you would beat them to death.
The police will contact you,
so handle all future procedures legally.
Darn it.
Let us go to my place for round two.
Goodness.
You look beaten half to death already...
before I even touched you.
How can you go home looking like that?
Gyu Rim will faint.
Hey.
I cannot just let you go today.
It is obvious...
- you are going to cause trouble. - Darn it.
As you felt earlier,
my fists are still quite useful.
What will it be?
Do you want to get beaten up more, or will you just come quietly?
Who is that scary thug in your room?
Gyu Rim's brother.
He is not a thug, and he is not scary at all.
He is just...
an idiot, an idiot.
So?
Whether he is a thug, an idiot, or Gyu Rim's brother,
why is he glaring like that in your room?
Well,
there is a reason for that.
He will be staying here for a while, so do not go and provoke him.
I will book a hotel for you, so will you stay there?
Is this Gyu Rim's family vacation home?
Is it an exclusive guest house for her family?
Why do her son and brother...
take turns staying here?
Keep your voice down.
Here. Go stay at a hotel.
Why would I go to a hotel when I have my own house?
Darn it...
Then you...
Tell me just one thing you want the most...
out of everything I own.
Why? You will give it to me if I keep my mouth shut?
Wow, what kind of person...
- does this guy think I am? - Is there nothing you want?
Do you really think I am that kind of...
The basketball shoes Stephen Curry...
wore in Game 6 of the 2015 NBA Finals...
when he won the championship.
The ones you went all the way to New York...
to win at auction. How much were they again?
- What is the second thing you want? - Nothing.
What a cold-hearted girl.
She picked the exact time we were out...
to pack up all her things and leave.
She did not even say goodbye.
They say you might not notice when someone moves in,
but you definitely notice when they move out.
You know,
when I think about how Gyu Young...
will never come back to this house...
It feels like there is a gaping hole right here, Gyu Rim.
The freezing wind is blowing right through.
She will call you, Father.
I will not answer even if she calls.
Do you think I have no pride?
I will just consider it as never having had her.
Do you think she is just completely happy...
after leaving like that?
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Thank you for welcoming me, Father and Mother.
I will be the most lovely, proud,
and beautiful daughter-in-law in the world.
Oh my, I am so happy today.
Mom, Dad, are you not...
completely smitten with our Gyu Young?
I am barely holding back from giving her a piggyback ride.
But my dear daughter-in-law,
while your new house is being remodelled,
you'll have to stay here with us...
- Won't that be uncomfortable? - Oh, of course it will be.
How could it not be?
Not at all. It won't be uncomfortable in the slightest,
and I actually love the idea.
Oh my, we keep calling her pretty,
and she just keeps saying the prettiest things.
What could possibly be good about living with your in-laws?
Oh, I mean it. I'm being sincere, Mother.
Your daughter went abroad to study, so if Sung Wook moved out too,
you two would have been so lonely.
Until the remodelling is finished, I'll live here with you...
and act as your daughter...
Please be patient with my shortcomings...
and take good care of me. Mom, Dad.
She called me Mom.
Honey, did you just call them Mom and Dad?
Well, I'm their daughter from now on,
so I can call you that, right? Mom, Dad.
I can't take it. I have to give you a piggyback ride.
- Come here. - Mother.
Oh my, let me hug you.
Mom.
Bring that ramyeon over here when it's done.
I'll have it as a snack. Put two eggs in it.
This is mine.
- Make your own, Father. - Why have you been acting...
so grumpy? Did you tag in for Gyu Young...
just to nag your father?
Why did you cheat in the first place?
A man with a wife and kids.
Why bring up the cheating whenever you see me?
Can't you see your father is...
struggling because of Gyu Young?
Why would a married man with a family...
see another woman?
If you hadn't met that woman, you wouldn't have gotten a divorce.
If you hadn't met that woman,
- none of us would have suffered. - Hey.
She's still technically your mother, so don't call her "that woman."
Why did you meet her in the first place?
I told you, your mother seduced me.
They say any tree will fall if you chop it ten times.
Your mother chopped at me...
- more than 50 times. - Are you a tree, Father?
You're a human being with reason and common sense,
aren't you?
Are you a bird, then?
Repeating the same thing over and over again.
Are you a parrot?
Oh, man.
Why are all my kids...
so determined to eat their one and only father alive?
My blood pressure is rising.
I should be the one starting a new family...
and getting out of this dump.
My stomach hurts.
Gosh.
My kids are so cheap.
They even ate all the canned tuna I had hidden away.
What's this?
What?
What is it?
Oh my, what is this?
Wow.
Wow. Oh, hey, what's with this beautiful lunchbox?
Someone dropped it off for you to eat.
Well, if you had something like this,
you should've told me sooner. You really.
I know this taste.
What?
Abalone with yuzu.
I've definitely tasted this somewhere before.
Oh, I know.
Pongdang Restaurant in Samcheok. This is from there, right?
This is exactly Mrs. Kang's cooking from Pongdang Restaurant, isn't it?
Right?
No?
Then who is it? Oh!
Oh! Poksak Restaurant in Jeju.
Hanggu Restaurant in Mokpo.
Wait...
Then, Nurungji Restaurant in Busan?
Which one?
Seriously, I've had this before.
Gyu Min, Gyu Oh is going to stay at my place for a while.
Make up a good excuse so Gyu Rim doesn't worry.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you so much.
I'm coming in.
Why don't you stop thinking and get some sleep?
There's chamomile tea in the thermos.
It'll help if you drink it when you can't sleep.
("Cosmos")
Books that put you right to sleep.
I personally recommend this one.
This is a squishy toy Gyeol left behind.
Take your anger out on it.
It'd be even better if you squeeze it...
as hard as your anger and break it.
I can just buy Gyeol a new one.
Take all your guilt and self-hatred about Han Gyu Oh out on it too.
You know how bad self-harm is for your body.
I know because I did it for eight years.
I do not care about Son Ji Yeol...
or the host bar owner.
I don't know, let's just sleep for now.
Let's think after we sleep.
Just close your eyes and sleep first.
I'll be guarding the living room.
Don't even dream about running away or anything like that.
(Tyrannosaurus)
That woman must be your mother.
She came by last time and asked if you were Gyu Rim.
But why did she pretend not to know you...
and just leave the lunchbox?
I didn't know you were out here. I looked all over for you.
Are you okay?
You didn't sleep a wink last night and kept tossing and turning.
You're going to collapse at this rate.
Don't worry too much about Seo Hyun.
She's fine. I saw her briefly at the office,
and she's doing perfectly fine.
Oh, and did I tell you that she left the hotel...
and went to Ji Hye's house?
Plus, Jung Woo is right there keeping a close eye on her,
so please don't worry too much.
I packed a lunchbox yesterday...
because I wanted to give it to Seo Hyun.
Oh, you did?
I took it all the way to her office.
But no matter how long I waited,
I couldn't get in touch with her.
So I gave that lunchbox...
to Gyu Rim.
To Gyu Rim?
I made it for Seo Hyun.
If Seo Hyun wouldn't take it, I should've just let it go.
Why did I...
It's not like Gyu Rim is a garbage disposal for leftovers.
I went all that way and couldn't even say I was her mother.
I was so scared she'd recognise me...
that I just ran away.
What kind of person am I?
Yoon Hee.
I don't even know who I am anymore.
I'm not Seo Hyun's mother, and I'm not Gyu Rim's mother either.
What kind of person am I?
Why would you think that?
You are Seo Hyun's mother, and you are Gyu Rim's mother too.
No matter how much I despised my ex-husband,
they're still my own flesh and blood.
How could I go 17 years...
without contacting them even once, completely ignoring their existence?
You did it to raise Seo Hyun well...
and be devoted to her.
That's why we never had any younger siblings for her.
I thought that was the reason.
But I don't think it is.
More than them...
my current life was just too precious to me.
The world I'm standing on right now...
is already as fragile as a sandcastle.
I was terrified they would show up and tear it all down.
I think I was just too scared of that.
I'm awful, right?
I'm disgusting, aren't I?
Honey,
should we go out for breakfast? Let's not cook.
Oh, a hotel. A hotel breakfast sounds nice.
Let's go to a hotel.
Honey.
Please give me some time.
I am so sorry to you...
that I cannot even look you in the eye, but...
Some time to think alone...
Please give me that.
What does that mean?
This girl, seriously.
Hey, Han Gyu Young. Who are you trying to ruin now...
by putting this all in here together?
I told you to do your own laundry. How many times do I have to...
Fine, Han Gyu Young.
Like you said, you are the one ruining your own life.
Live your life however you want.
I am done.
Just like you wanted,
you and I are done here.
Hey, I opened my eyes this morning, and I was so shocked.
It was not my room in our awful house.
Yes. Yes.
The maid even brought me freshly squeezed green juice...
for room service,
and the room has a marble bathroom with a bathtub...
and a walk-in closet as big as a playground.
Hey, first of all,
I love that my family is not in my sight.
I do not have to hear their annoying voices,
and I do not have to see their tiresome faces.
Oh, Se Hee. I will call you back later.
What is wrong with your clothes?
Why do you think?
Did you not even check the size before buying the clothes?
No, they said it was the only one left,
so I just snatched it up.
When that man wore it,
it looked incredibly cool.
That man?
What man?
Did you see some man?
No, it is not that.
Another man was trying to buy it.
Hold on a second.
Did you perhaps confuse my size with some other guy's size?
- Am I you? - I ought to...
How dare you yell at me?
What is with your hand?
Were you trying to hit me just now?
Gosh, seriously. This is frustrating.
Gosh.
Do you hit women?
If you do something to deserve it, you should be hit.
Hey, my father said...
women and dried pollack must be beaten...
once every three days.
What?
Why would you hit me?
What gives you the right to hit me?
Why would you make a call like that to Se Ra, anyway?
Why? Are you embarrassed?
You old geezer. Do you not even think of me?
What? You bought Se Ra a necklace.
And the exact same brand as mine, with the exact same design.
Why? Were you afraid you would get confused?
Keep quiet and go inside.
- Let us talk inside. - Why should I go inside?
Gyu Young is going to find out eventually...
that her father-in-law is a massive womanizer.
Hey. You people.
Darn it.
Why are you hitting me? Fine, beat me. Beat me.
Let us both die today, you jerk.
Hey, let go of me. Let go.
Who are you texting every night?
- Who is it? - Hey. My gosh!
Do you not know what privacy is?
Why are you looking at someone else's phone?
He must have stayed up all night like that.
He is giving off samurai vibes, and Joseon swordsman vibes.
Wow. Sitting like that, his back must not even hurt.
His eyes are still shooting lasers...
that look like they could wipe out the world,
and he is sitting with his fists clenched like this.
If you just put a sword in his hand,
he looks like he would unknowingly kill someone.
Stay near a bad guy and you get stabbed...
You have heard that saying, right? He is dangerous. Very dangerous.
You know my intuition is almost at a psychic level, right?
Just make up a good excuse and get him out of this house quickly.
I told you to go stay at a hotel.
Why do you not listen?
How can I leave you alone in this dangerous house...
and escape by myself?
I am telling you, he gives off terrorist vibes.
I am the one holding the knife, do I not look dangerous?
What?
If you insult our goofy Gyu Oh one more time,
this knife will not just be chopping green onions.
If I call your Gyu Oh a goof ball...
twice, you would kill me?
Now that you are crazy in love, friends and everything else...
are useless.
Our 15-year friendship is useless too.
Because of that damn family selfishness,
our country cannot make it into the G7.
Gosh...
It is delicious.
So annoying.
Did you stay up all night like this?
Does your back not hurt?
Well, I guess you do not want to sit face-to-face with me...
and eat right now.
The kimchi stew is on the stove, okay?
The rice is in the rice cooker,
and the side dishes are in the fridge,
so help yourself.
You are scared of yourself too, right?
Because you are scared of yourself, you are...
staying completely still like this.
If you cause more trouble here, then it cannot be fixed anymore.
Because then Gyu Rim will find out too.
That is a relief.
That you and I have the same destination.
That Gyu Rim doesn't cry anymore.
That Gyu Rim doesn't get hurt anymore.
Let's not stray from the path and just...
try to make it to our destination together.
As for hitting you yesterday, once we arrive...
I'll formally apologize to you then.
You will be connected to voicemail.
Gosh, Gyu Young. Seriously.
She won't answer my calls or read my texts.
Being so cold-hearted, she's the exact...
spitting image of her mother, I swear.
Fine, fine.
Let's just say she doesn't exist. She doesn't exist.
What? I have 2 sons and 2 daughters.
My kids are 2 sons and 2 daughters.
Are you going to give this radish kimchi to that guy too?
You know, that knockoff. The guy in the tracksuit.
No.
What's the address of that guy's restaurant?
I really need to go check it out with my own eyes.
Why would you go there, Father?
Well, he might become my son-in-law, so I should look into him properly.
See how big the restaurant is, find out what his sales are like.
There is absolutely nothing going on between him and me.
He's never going to be your son-in-law,
so please don't overreact.
He says he likes you.
And you and Gyeol like him too, apparently.
No, we don't.
That was in the past, not anymore.
He has absolutely nothing to do with me.
- He's not a married man, is he? - Father, please.
Hey, why are you yelling at me?
Am I that easy of a target?
Just because I have no money and no job,
everyone looks down on me.
Even so, I'm the father who brought you...
into this world, your father.
It's so unfair, it really is.
You just got your spit all over the radish kimchi.
Since your spit is in this,
you have to eat it all yourself, Father.
How am I supposed to eat all of this?
Hey.
How can I eat all this?
Hi.
This is hot cocoa, but...
I bought way too much.
Let's share it.
I have enough money to buy my own cocoa.
I told you, it's just because I bought too much.
Well, if I drink all of this by myself...
and get a blood sugar spike, will you take responsibility?
Fine.
Then I'll just take it all home by myself...
and drink 30 cups a day.
You don't care if someone else gets diabetes...
or not, do you?
I...
I'm not going to you, Mu Jin.
I'm absolutely not going.
So let's stop this, Mu Jin.
Not even nice words, but always mean words,
hurtful words.
I want to stop doing that too.
Please, just let me go, Mu Jin.
No.
Mu Jin.
Mean words, painful words, hurtful words.
Say them all you want.
Just do not get hurt by your own words.
Still, I wanted to see you for a long time today,
so I put some effort into my appearance...
You could at least think about my effort...
and be a little nice to me, can you not?
Even for just five minutes.
(456 Geumje-dong 4ga)
If you think I will get tired of this,
you should drop that thought.
Even if rejected every day, I will keep trying.
I will never be an idiot again and...
I will never lose you again.
(456 Geumje-dong 4ga)
Yes, you called, Grandma?
I was in class, so I could not answer. I am sorry.
Hee Na, I heard you are dating a thug these days.
A thug?
Do not even think about denying it, okay?
I heard it clearly from Gyu Oh.
Oh, this is so warm.
It feels like my blood circulation is improving all on its own.
Did Gyu Oh really say that?
That I am dating a thug these days?
He did, you know?
He said there's this crazy thug, right?
And this guy does not know his place and likes you an awful lot, Hee Na.
And he said you are also completely head over heels for him.
He said I should call your parents right away...
to teach that thug a lesson...
and tear you two apart. What should I do?
Should I tell your parents...
about this shocking news?
No.
Han Gyu Oh does not know anything and misspoke.
The person I am dating right now is not a thug.
He is really cool, kind,
- and a good person, Grandma. - Excuse me.
Could you turn up the temperature...
- a little higher? - Yes.
Oh my. Goodness, this is amazing.
My muscles are all relaxing, and my whole body is melting.
Where was I?
Anyway, never mind that.
Before I contact your parents,
you need to break up with that thug right this instant.
I am telling you, he is not a thug.
You will like him too when you see him.
You said it yourself before. You vouch for...
Anyway, I cannot tell you right now,
but please wait just a little bit.
- If you wait just a little bit... - Oh my?
You are already completely blinded by love.
I really need to call your parents...
- or step in myself. - Grandma.
If you really want to date someone, do not date some random guy.
You should see Gyu Oh instead.
Gyu Oh?
What? Is it already over?
- Yes, it is over. - Could I do it just one more time?
It feels so good that I do not want to get up.
Yes, go ahead.
Thank you. So, what do you say?
Do you not like Gyu Oh?
You are saying that because you do not know him well.
He might not have a decent job yet,
but a job is something he can just find.
He will never let you go hungry, Hee Na.
He is the kind of guy who will provide for you.
For a young man, he is thoughtful and hardworking.
He is kind and knows how to respect his elders.
Compared to that total thug you are seeing,
he is 100, no, 1,000 times better.
Oh, I told you before. Right after our Heung Sik,
he is the one guy I can personally vouch for.
Yes, you did.
You said that since you vouch for him,
I can rest assured.
I have matchmake five couples so far.
They had babies as cute as bunnies,
and you have no idea how well they are all living.
I understand, Grandma.
I will break up with that thug right away,
so please make sure to set me up with Han Gyu Oh.
Yes, yes.
Oh my, you made a great decision.
Yes, yes, do not worry.
Thank you, Grandma.
Oh my.
Wow, lying here in peace,
I just saved a girl who was about to go to ruin.
Oh my.
Oh, right. Your nephew. No, no. I mean, our boss...
he is going to the US...
because of his kids. Is that confirmed by any chance?
Yes, he is going.
So I am...
thinking of taking over this store.
With something this good,
how could I let someone else have it?
Let us stick together until the end. Please help me out.
Let us do this together, Director Song.
Yes, ma'am.
Wow, Han Gyu Oh.
What were you even thinking,
trying to tattle on me to my parents?
Gosh, seriously.
(Kwon Hee Na)
The call cannot be connected, so you will be connected to voicemail.
Why is he not answering?
(Are you busy? You must be really busy.)
(Han Gyu Oh? Hello?)
The number one is not disappearing.
You're not answering your phone. You're not reading my messages.
Are you sick? Did something happen to you?
What?
I am going crazy with worry, so please call me back soon.
(Communication, Sharing, Rainbow Dreams)
And no matter what happens between us,
I think we are meant to be,
so just give up and surrender, Han Gyu Oh.
Hey, you are spilling it.
Thank you, Gyu Seo.
No way, seriously.
This is so good.
- What is this? - What do you think it is?
Does the name sound like a brand name to you?
Ha Yo Won, Lee Hyo Jin, Gong Su Jeong, Lim Mi Na,
Shin Ye Seul, Han Yi Seul, Kim Chae Won, Moon Ji Won...
Gosh.
Did you get the message?
What is this?
The names of the girls who told me to give this to you.
Am I your delivery service?
You should have said I wouldn't accept it.
Why did you go through the trouble of bringing it?
Even earlier, I had a huge pile of these...
and I gave them all away to the other kids.
Yes, you are such a big shot.
Let's step outside for a second. I have something to tell you.
Me too. I have something to tell you too.
- What do you want to talk about? - You go first.
- You go first. - You are older, so you go first.
You brought it up first, so you go.
Okay, fine. Then let's say it at the same time.
In 3, 2, 1.
- You are hiding something, right? - You are hiding something, right?
- What is it? - What is it?
- Don't even think about lying. - Don't even think about lying.
Okay, okay.
- I will just go first. - No, I will go first.
Alright, you go first, then.
No, you go first.
Let's say it at the same time again, then.
In 3, 2, 1.
- I told Mu Jin about Gyu Oh. - I met Gyu Rim's biological mother.
I even got her phone number.
You met Gyu Rim's biological mother?
- And you got her phone number? - You told Mu Jin about Gyu Oh?
How much did you tell him?
She didn't even tell Gyu Rim...
that she was her mother before leaving?
After coming all that way? Why?
I don't know about that.
Gyu Rim's mother remarried...
and seems to have a family of her own.
Abandoning such a beautiful wife...
for a woman who looks like a witch...
Is our dad completely crazy?
How do you know she looks like a witch?
You don't even know what our mom looks like.
What kind of mother is she? A woman like that.
When you were little, you used to run away from home...
and cause a scene looking for her.
Do you know how hard it was for Gyu Rim...
- because of you? - Me?
When?
I never did that.
All right. End of discussion.
So did you tell Mom that you are Han Gyu Seo?
No.
I lied and said I was Kim Gyu Seo for now.
Were you afraid she'd know who you are...
if you said Han Gyu Seo? What if she knew?
"So you are that witch's son." "You son of my enemy."
"You are dead to me today."
Were you afraid she would curse and hit you?
Why did you tell Mr. Mu Jin about Gyu Oh?
I do not know either.
He caught me crying because I was upset...
about Gyu Oh.
How could you tell him everything just because he caught you?
The sunlight was so warm...
how could the traveller not take off his coat?
What are you talking about?
Mr. Mu Jin is so reliable and warm...
I just started blabbing without even realising it.
You know that if there is one thing about me,
it is that I can keep a secret, right?
I was shocked myself after I told him everything.
Think about what happened with Gyeol.
What would we have done without Mr. Mu Jin?
Now Mr. Mu Jin feels like family, like an older brother.
He is like a guardian presence for our family.
So,
is Gyu Oh at Mr. Mu Jin's place right now?
And he lied to Gyu Rim about going on a trip?
If you do something to deserve it, you should be hit.
Hey, my father said...
women and dried pollack must be beaten...
once every three days.
Let us both die today, you jerk.
Hey, let go of me. Let go.
Hey, let go. Who are you texting every night?
- Who is it? - Hey. My gosh!
Do you not know what privacy is?
Why are you looking at someone else's phone?
Customer number 15,
- your iced Americano is ready. - Yes.
Thank you.
I am sorry.
It is a shame, but this time, I do not think I can go to Milan.
I know. Instead,
I will definitely go to Paris no matter what.
Okay. It is time for my guest to arrive...
Let's talk later.
Have a good day.
You are here?
Oh, my.
What is with this super old-school setup?
I knew you would bring it back.
How could a size that fits me fit Sung Wook?
Oh, but did we not agree to meet at three o'clock?
Do you have other plans besides me?
No, I do not have any other plans.
I do not think so. I think you got the time wrong.
Oh, were you planning to pick up women here?
- Should I get out of your way? - What are you talking about?
Just give me back those clothes.
Memorizing foreign words you do not even understand to flirt...
is a completely Stone Age tactic. Jo Heung Sik.
With such a cheap and outdated sense of style,
are you trying to seduce a caveman?
Save all that nonsense for when you go home...
and just hand over the shopping bag.
What you want to do and what you can do...
are two different things. If you want to be happy,
please stick to what you can actually do.
Do you need me to translate that for you?
Right.
You are right.
You cannot have everything just because you want it,
and having everything does not make you happy either.
But...
When will you ever grow up?
Sitting with a married woman for too long...
will only cause unnecessary misunderstandings.
I will get going.
Oh, and by the way, my mom saw your mom,
and she said she was cold, distant, and heartless,
exactly like a carbon copy of you.
Is your nasty attitude the power of genetics?
What do you mean by that? Where did she see my mom?
I asked where she saw her.
(Suragan Side Dishes)
Why did Mom come to see you?
I am asking why Mom came to see you.
She was so cold to me,
so what is her reason for visiting you?
What did Mom say?
Did she see you living in this pathetic state...
and offer you money?
Did she offer you a few hundred thousand?
Did she say she would give you a building?
Please be quiet, ma'am.
If you yell one more time, I will call the police.
Darn it.
I asked how much Mom said she would give you.
Han Gyu Rim.
Darn it.
Hey, can you not hear me? Hey, hello.
Hey, what did Mom say she would give you.
- I do not have a mom. - What?
Because my mom died a long time ago. If you want to talk about your mom,
go talk to your siblings, ma'am. Stop chattering so loudly in here.
Gosh.
It is so offensive how you keep calling me ma'am.
You really are cutting ties for good.
Fine, if we are cutting ties,
let us do it properly so there is no lingering affection.
Gyeol's Mom. That is exactly what I want, too.
Gyeol's Mom.
If we bump into each other on the street,
just try acting like you know me. Gyeol's Mom.
Darn it.
If I ever find out later that Mom gave you anything,
I will not let it slide. I will sue you.
Gosh.
She just left a lunchbox.
Why?
She was afraid I would find out she is my mom,
so she even came wearing sunglasses.
Not one year,
not two years,
but showing up after 17 years...
A mother should not do that to her child.
A mother...
cannot do that.
She is still my mom, though.
She is my mom.
This sports line maintains our existing functionality...
while being perfectly suited for everyday wear,
with a lifewear and stylewear concept in mind.
As you have seen,
we aimed to showcase a wider variety of styles...
this fall, and we expect the customer response...
to be just as positive. Accordingly, we have also...
secured a stable supply of inventory.
So that each store can achieve great results this season,
we will also do our best. That is all.
Excuse me, can I try this on?
Oh, this is very nice.
Please secure inventory for this one.
- Yes, understood. - Us, too.
Well, the response is not bad.
I thought you would drop work and everything else...
and run away somewhere, to hide.
I know how to separate my personal and professional life.
Is that so?
I am glad you did not take after me in that regard.
If you have nothing else to say, I will take my leave.
Your mother left home.
I do not know where she is right now.
Well, you left once, and I left once, so, to be fair,
I guess it was your mother's turn to leave.
Are you two getting a divorce?
Well...
Your mother seems to be considering it,
but I do not know.
It is not because of you.
Okay?
It probably will not happen, but even if it does,
it is not because of you.
Anyway, stop burdening your friend...
and come home.
Seo Hyun.
I really don't know.
What it means to be a parent...
or what it means to be a child.
I'm heading out, so please get the car ready.
Dad.
Write up the report and submit it by tomorrow.
- Welcome. - Hello.
Why are you drinking in broad daylight?
You're here?
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Do you happen to believe in fortune-telling?
I completely believe in it.
Clink.
They said my fortune...
has a sword in it.
That's why I cut off my son...
and severed ties with my friend of 40 years.
Oh, me too.
They said my fortune has scissors in it,
so I get cut off by everyone close to me...
If it's a friend of 40 years,
that's a best friend you've known longer than your son.
Why did you go as far as cutting ties?
Because he was talking such nonsense.
As if ruining his own life wasn't enough,
why would he try to ruin someone else's son's life?
That jerk.
How could he offer his wife's daughter...
to my son?
If it's his wife's daughter, isn't it his own daughter?
Well, anyway...
The more I think about it, the angrier I get.
Both my son and my friend.
How could they all do this to me?
Are all men like this?
When they go crazy over a woman, do they lose their minds?
Well, I don't have any experience with that.
But I do understand that feeling of betrayal.
I've been stabbed in the back so many times.
I've been betrayed and backstabbed so often.
By the guy I met through business, my son, and my friend.
I know some guys...
who will never betray you.
Should I introduce you?
Awesome.
These guys will absolutely never betray you.
Is there anything else you like?
- How about that pink one? - What exactly do you do?
Some people even call me Santa Claus.
You said your name was Seok Joong, right?
You remembered.
I should at least remember your name if we are going to be friends.
Let's just be friends. No.
Here, let's be friends.
Well, it's a two-year difference, so why not?
Let's be friends.
Friend.
- But what is your name, friend? - Me?
(Gyu Rim)
Are you enjoying your trip?
Are you eating well?
I heard the temperature drops at night,
so be careful not to catch a cold.
Nothing is wrong, right?
For someone who doesn't even like travelling...
to suddenly go on a trip...
Honestly...
I am worried.
I am afraid someone might take my Gyu Oh away.
I am afraid someone might ask you to be their brother.
I am really worried.
That will be 24 dollars.
Even if a more capable and cooler woman appears...
and offers to buy you snacks and bread,
do not ever be swayed...
and come back home to me...
right away.
Run back without looking back.
I will do much, much better from now on.
Gyu Oh.
I am sorry, Gyu Rim.
Do you want a fried egg?
Hey, slow down. I am not going to steal it.
I am not going to die.
I am going to live.
Who said otherwise?
I am never going to die. I will not die even if it kills me.
Hey, but I am starving to death.
You did not eat it all, right?
- I ate it all. - What?
- Hey. - There is nothing there.
(456 Geumje-dong 4ga)
Gyu Rim.
What?
Gyu Min told me...
you went on a trip to Namhae and would be back in a week.
I was going to come back in a week,
but some weird woman showed up...
and tried to tempt me by offering to buy me snacks and bread,
asking me to be her brother.
Then I remembered you told me to come back right away,
to run back without looking back.
So I ran back as fast as I could.
What happened to your face?
Where did you get hurt?
Who did this?
Something happened, right?
A lot of things happened.
Like what?
What happened?
It is too long to explain right now.
I am dead tired right now, so tired I cannot say another word.
Gyu Oh.
Not today, but at your birthday party when you turn 100.
Can I answer you then?
Okay.
You can do that.
To hear your answer,
I will have to live a very long time, right?
It is enough that you came back.
Coming back safely like this...
is all that matters.
This is enough for today, Gyu Oh.
You have been through a lot.
Welcome home.
(Love on the Menu)
You should give up on my brother, Ms. Kwon.
You told me not to give up before.
But he will not give up.
I think I was scammed into this marriage.
You are the one who scammed him.
If my mom and dad get divorced, is it because of me?
Since when did our Seo Hyun become so mature?
Can you tell me how to make him run away from me?
I am going to do a proper background check.
To see if he is someone I can approve of...
or someone I need to keep away from her.
- I really want to be happy today. - Let us see how we end up...
and take this all the way to the end.